You write something here first, boss.
- It should come from your heart.
- Boss, come on.
You write songs, don't you?
Maybe you can share your talent
when it comes to words.
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
[JORDAN] We've known
each other for so long.
There are good times
and bad.
We've seen it all.
And I can't help
but admire how you rose above it.
I can't help
but fall.
So let me take this chance to say…
I think I love you.
And if someday, life gets heavy,
or when the road is hard to see,
when your world is full of questions,
you can always run to me.
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
Auntie…
Can we invite Papa
to my moving-up ceremony?
I got high honors.
[ENRICO] Remember this, son.
From now on, I'll always be here for you.
[PRECIOUS]
Don't get your hopes up too much.
Don't expect him to be allowed
to meet you all the time.
[ENRICO] You're right, Precious.
I deceived you.
But even though I wasn't honest with you,
the love I have for my children
and for you…
is real.
[BILLY] You got hurt. Are you all right?
I'm all right, Billy.
But you have to look at this.
[BILLY] So they've been keeping
an eye on me for a while now?
Auntie Pres, right from the start,
they've been planning this all along.
That's why we need to be more careful.
We don't know why they're going after you.
[MARIELA] They're living lavishly.
They're living a luxurious life.
And now, they have your father too!
While us?
[SOBS] We've got nothing left!
Now I understand why you're
so furious at that Billy!
I'll kill them!
I'll kill them both!
- [BEA] Ma! Ma!
- [SOBBING]
No one's dying.
[SHUSHING]
That's why, Ma, you have to promise me
that you'll leave our revenge up to me.
[OLIVER] It's here, it's ready!
[OLIVER] Ta-da!
What's that?
Since you weren't able
to come to my birthday parties,
I'll just show them to you instead!
This here is from my first birthday!
It was at Auntie's house before.
This here is Jordan, Billy's best friend.
Good buddies!
After that,
we started celebrating
my birthdays at the cemetery
so we could celebrate it with Mama.
All of my birthdays are fun.
Except for when I turned seven.
Why? What happened when you turned seven?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I got rushed to the hospital.
That's when we found out
that I'm diabetic.
But, see, I'm really strong
and bounced back.
I even won during Family Day.
Nailed it, huh?
I think Billy danced back then…
Like this, one, two, three, four, yeah!
Try to do it with me, Pa.
Three, two, one, go!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- Let's go again.
- Is this right?
One, two, three, four, five, six!
- That was great!
- [LAUGHTER]
Wait, what about this?
[OLIVER] That was my last birthday.
You know,
that birthday
was both happy and sad.
Because it was my birthday,
but also the day Mom died.
You know what happened to Mom, right?
She died while giving birth to me.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry, Oliver.
I'm sorry that I wasn't there
when you all needed me.
When your mom needed me.
[OLIVER] Pa,
did you ever love Mom?
You know what, Oliver?
I loved your mother.
It's a shame that I didn't have the chance
to ask for her forgiveness.
Billy always says that
Mom is watching over us from heaven.
I'm sure she can see how sorry you are.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Stay here, I'll get some water.
- [OLIVER] Here, Pa, look.
I look just like you.
We're both good-looking.
[ENRICO] When did you
start wearing glasses?
I'm just like you.
We're both wearing glasses. Both handsome.
Ha!
So you've always been copying me?
- Yes.
- What about him?
Is he courting your sister?
- No. They're just friends.
- Hmm? Really?
Promise.
- I promise.
- [CHUCKLES]
He needs to ask for
my permission first, okay?
- I promise. I promise.
- Is that okay?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Bye, Pa! I'll see you tomorrow.
Ask your sister
for her permission first, okay?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you, Precious.
[OLIVER] I hope Billy
is with us next time.
Hug?
Hug. Hug.
- Fist bump.
[OLIVER] Fist bump!
- Boom.
- Boom. [CHUCKLES]
- Bye, Pa!
- Be good, okay?
- Yes!
- Okay, go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ENRICO] Take care!
- [CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GATE CREAKS]
[TENSE MUSIC FADES]
[BILLY] What are you wearing?
- What's wrong?
- Fix it.
- You should've borrowed mine.
- What is that? You could've--
Hi, guys.
- Hi.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Just want to let you guys know that
I'm very excited about this partnership.
And also, just to formalize everything,
with this agreement, I acquired
the exclusive franchise right of LoveList
for the entire
North American region, right?
- Exclusive territory.
- [PETER] All right.
But the brand ownership stays with us.
- [PETER] Of course.
- That's part of our agreement. Yes.
And you guys will be operating
our global standards.
- [BILLY] Mm-hmm.
- Marketing templates.
Platform architecture.
Expansion strategies.
Yeah, but everything needs to be aligned.
Yes, of course.
I'm not here to change the brand.
- I'm just here to scale it.
- Perfect. Okay.
As long as we protect
what makes LoveList LoveList.
Right.
Well, thirty million
is a serious investment.
Yes, it is.
Thank you so much again for your trust.
We won't take it lightly.
- [PETER] Right.
- Yes, thank you.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- Yes, I think we're ready. Let's go?
- Of course.
- Ms. Billy, it's ready.
- Perfect timing.
- Perfect.
- All right. Thank you.
- Let's go.
[BLAIRE] Okay, you go first. Let's go!
[REPORTER] Hi, sir!
[REPORTER] Turn here! Smile!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- [BILLY] Go ahead.
- [PETER] Ah, thank you.
- Okay.
- [BILLY] Thank you.
[BLAIRE] Go upstairs.
Hi. How are you?
[BLAIRE] Come on, everyone!
[PEOPLE CLAPPING, CHEERING]
Let's take a photo!
- Photo?
- Okay.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- [HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLAIRE] Smile!
- Now, sir, you can have the mic.
- Ah, okay. Sure.
Hello. Check?
Hi. To our press,
to our beloved journalists,
our social media influencers,
and reporters,
thank you so much for being here today
as we…
as LoveList
goes from a regional brand
to a global brand.
- [BLAIRE] Awesome! Whoo!
- Thank you!
[PEOPLE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
You may take your seats.
I'm excited. Thank you.
And we can sign the contract now.
[PETER] All right.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[PEOPLE CLAPPING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICK]
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC FADES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CRISELDA] My God, I was panicking.
- [BEA] What's happening here?
[CRISELDA]
What if you'd actually killed her?
Ma! Wait a minute. What's happening here?
We should be the ones asking you that.
I'll let you sleep here
in my unit for tonight,
but you should be gone by the morning!
Wait, Ms. Criselda. Don't do this to us.
You haven't paid rent
for two months already!
If I'd only known that you were criminals,
I never would have let you live here!
They're living lavishly.
[SOBS] They have a beautiful house.
They're living a luxurious life.
And now, they have your father too!
While us?
[SOBS] We've got nothing left!
Look at what we have, Bea!
[CRIES] Nothing!
Ma…
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC
CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
- [ALL] Cheers!
- [GLASSES CLINKING]
- [MARJ] Whoo-hoo!
- [RALPH] Yeah!
- Congrats!
- [RALPH] Whoo!
[CHARM] Gosh, Billy,
the amount earlier was huge.
- You can retire now.
- [GLASSES THUDDING]
What do you mean, retire? I wish.
As long as that mischievous kid
is still studying,
retirement isn't an option.
Come on. Oliver's smart, right?
He'll qualify for a scholarship.
- Just relax, girl.
- [CHARM] True.
How about
- we go to the beach?
- [MARJ SQUEALING]
- Oh, that could work!
- [MARJ] Yes!
Yes, Oliver really is smart.
But even if he gets into
the Kingsley scholarship program,
the daily expenses are no joke.
Unless you're willing to chip in.
You guys? Pitch in?
You know what? Let's do it.
When was your last beach trip?
Back before Oliver even learned to talk.
- That's it, right?
- You're so dramatic!
- [CHARM] Yeah.
- Hey, come on.
Let's go to the beach so I can wear
the outfits I bought online!
You know, I'm sure this will just end up
being just another daydream again.
Let's please make it happen
this time. Okay?
- Oh!
- I'm in!
- [CHARM] Let's go!
- [TONI] Right?
Hey, you're getting me drunk
just to get me to agree.
- You're so obvious.
- Huh? What?
- Why just mine? Refill yours too!
- Fine!
- Well, just a suggestion.
- [SOFT THUD]
Book that flight.
You know Billy's details.
- Come on.
- Yes! Yeah!
- Marj, go.
- [CLAPPING]
- Go, go, go, go! Yes!
- Seriously? Hey, don't!
- We can't all go together--
- Go!
- No, no, no, no!
- Relax, relax!
- We can't!
- Relax!
- Oh, look at this.
- Why a boat?
Where are we going? Are you serious?
- [TONI] We'll handle it.
- Toni.
- [TONI] Just sit there.
- Where, where?
No one's going to approve your leave!
- No, no! Just chill.
- [TONI] It's been a long time--
- Hey, don't!
- Let's talk about it for a sec.
- But have a drink first.
- I don't want to!
I don't want to drink!
You're tricking me.
Okay, let's drink together now!
- Cheers!
- Let's go to the beach!
- Let's go!
[CHANTING] Let's go to the beach!
- Let's go to the beach!
- [GLASSES CLINKING]
- When? When are we going?
[BILLY GIGGLES]
[MUSIC TURNS STIRRING]
[PETER] Why? What are you looking at?
[MAN] There's a lady there.
Um…
- [PETER] Is she pretty?
- [MAN] Of course.
All right. Just show her to me.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll buy one.
Thanks.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
One, please.
[RACY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA] It's so hot.
So hot.
It's so hot in here.
It really is.
[BEA SIGHS]
So, you believe in online dating?
Hmm?
[BEA HALF-LAUGHS] I guess.
That's why I'm using this app.
[RACY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is it any good?
I hope so.
Let's see.
I hope I can find
my match.
I can't believe you're single.
Yes.
I'm single.
- Mm-hmm.
- Super single.
And you?
Yeah.
No, I'm single.
Oh!
- You're single too?
- Mm-hmm.
[RACY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mm!
So that means
I don't need this app anymore.
Ooh, you're a feisty one, I see.
- [BEA] Mm?
- Mm.
As the saying goes,
"Life is short."
So if you want something,
you should get it.
Get it?
Oh, I get it.
You get it?
Mm-hmm.
[BEA GIGGLES]
Bea.
Peter.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BAND PLAYING]
[JORDAN SINGING]
♪ Why is it like that? ♪
♪ So many are… ♪
[VALERIE] Maybe I was
hoping eventually,
you'll learn to love me more
than you love her.
But what's written there is true.
But you didn't write this
to express Robbie's feelings for me.
What's holding you back?
Why can't you just be
honest with her?
Thank you.
[PRECIOUS] Your father said
he'll never leave you guys again.
That will be the end of it.
This is going to hurt Oliver.
Is it just Oliver who will get hurt?
Or you too?
Giving you a chance
was already a huge ask.
Please. I need more
time with him.
I'll deal with them.
Billy is going down.
[MARIELA] As long as your father
and his mistress are together,
I will never be okay.
Mariela, please.
Leave us alone.
If it had happened to you,
you'd be angry too.
What's your real problem
with me and my daughter?
[MARIELA]
This should've been ours.
So we won't stop
until we get what is rightfully ours!